Kim: The yard’s wonderful, I love it.
Leo: Is there a garage?
Barbara: Oh yes, there’s a big garage over there.
Kim: You lived in this house, is that right, Mrs. …?
Barbara	: Miss Travers.
But call me Barbara, dear.
Yes, I lived here. A long time ago. Now I live in town.
Let’s go inside the house…
This is the living room. It’s a lovely room, very bright.
Kim: Mmm... I love the furniture, the old sofa, the armchairs, the fireplace.
Barbara: And this is the library…
Leo: Wow! There’s a library, Kim!
Barbara: And this is the kitchen.
It’s very big, as you can see.
Kim: Is there a dishwasher?
Barbara: No, there isn’t. It’s an old house, you see.
Leo: Never mind. I think it’s nice. Is there a bathroom downstairs?
Barbara: Yes, there’s one downstairs and there are three upstairs.
Kim: Are there any neighbors with children?
Barbara: No, there aren’t any neighbors near here.
But there are some families with children in town.
Kim: That’s great. We have two children.
Barbara	: Very nice, dear. Now, let’s go upstairs…